Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Asta visits the village of Neon, home to Rebecca and her younger siblings.
Coincidentally, Gosha's beloved little sister Marie lives there as well.
Kay, come on and...
Get away from her right now, you scum!
That night, a strange tragedy befell Neon.
It's time... for you... to die.
We don't even live here!
What? There's snow everywhere. Where'd it all come from? It's not even winter yet.
Hey! Stop it! What are you doing out here?
It's the children! They're missing!
No.
How exciting. I just love making new friends.
What is this?
Ha
Thank you.
Why would they run off at this hour?
Possies!
Roland! Where are you?
Not playing hide-and-seek, I'm guessing.
Die, scum.
I will never allow you to marry my sister.
Come on, Ghosh! This is so not the time!
There is nothing in this world more important than my marine.
Nothing.
Can someone please tell me what's wrong with this village?
They need snow at this time of year? That is just absurd.
Hey, Noelle. What are you doing in neon?
Uh, just passing through, seeing the sights, that sort of thing, you know.
Asta, who is this?
A friend from the Magic Knights!
Noelle, this is my friend Rebecca.
His friend? His friend?
Uh...
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hey, listen.
A little while ago, I saw a bunch of kids headed toward the mountains.
What was that about?
Was there some kind of late-night festival?
The kids!
I have a festival of blood plant.
Stop that!
The hag!
Sister Granny!
The snow isn't natural.
I can sense some kind of spell in it.
One that controls people.
But only children whose magic has not yet developed.
Several of ours have disappeared as well.
Why would someone be spiriting all of these children away?
Wait, Crone.
You lost some of yours?
Marie better not have been one of them.
Unfortunately, she was.
Damn you!
You decrepit old fool!
How could you let this happen to her?
Stop! Please!
So quick to resort to violence!
You truly are hopeless!
You can hit me if you want to,
but that's not going to bring them back!
It won't help Marie!
No, it won't.
But it will make me feel a hell of a lot better!
Get off of him!
What do you think you're doing?
Asta, you will die.
Hey now, why don't we stop for a second
to take a deep breath and cool off a little bit!
We're magic knights, after all.
We have to learn to remain calm.
You got it?
Well done.
I like this boy.
Calm, huh?
All right then.
I knew you'd come around.
I'll kill you very calmly.
That's not what I meant!
That's right, Brad.
I'm gonna make it hurt.
No, please stop!
We're wasting time!
We have to start looking for clues!
Oh yeah.
Like it's gonna be that easy.
Hmm.
I told Marie to keep her magic mirror with her at all times.
The snow will interfere with transmission magic.
But if we track down the mana in the mirror...
then we should be able to find her.
There, you see?
Fine, you were right!
But don't think for a second
that's gonna keep me from stomping the life out of you maggot!
I'll come too.
The church's children are my responsibility.
Thanks, sister.
But maybe you should just let us handle it.
No, the hag is infuriating, but she does have her uses.
Really?
But isn't she kind of... old?
I can still teach you youngsters a thing or two.
Lasta?
Between Marco's immaturity and Luca's stubborn streak,
I'm really worried about them.
What am I going to do?
If anything happens to those two...
Hey, get it together!
You hear me?
I promise you, I'll bring your brother and sister back.
No moping, okay?
I don't think they would want that.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go now.
You're not going to leave me behind, are you?
You can't fly on your own either.
You want to be a dangler like him?
Hmm.
There's always a chance the village may be attacked again while we're gone.
Please stay here and look after it for me.
Oh, and let the magic knights know what's up!
Asta, we're counting on you!
Right.
I'm stuck here with her.
Oh, wow.
I can't believe how many new friends I've made.
Now, let's play nice, okay?
Where am I?
This isn't the church.
How did I get here?
And why does everyone look so strange?
So sweet.
Who is that man?
Good little children now, thanks to my magic.
Did he cast a spell on everyone?
Then why?
Oh, right.
The mirror my brother gave me.
He said it would protect me from magic a little bit.
Think of it as your big brother when I'm not there.
That's why I'm awake.
Oh, dear.
My spell's worn off this one.
Why is that?
It's too bad, really.
If I can't use my magic to make you a good girl, we can't be friends.
You want to be my friend, right?
No, not that way.
You shouldn't use spells to make people do what you want.
If you do that, you're not a real friend at all.
You don't belong here, you horrible little monster.
No friend of mine would ever say something like that.
Now, now.
Don't lose your temper, Mish.
We don't want to damage the merchandise.
Do I have to do all your thinking for you?
No, please.
I'm sorry.
This one's our star.
A lot of power for a kid.
Any more like her, we'll be Richmond by the time we're done.
That kid hardly has any magic.
I told you to get the ones who were loaded, and this is what you bring me, really?
I'm sorry, Boro.
We don't need this trash.
Bye, kid!
Brother or not, keep wasting my time and I'll kill you.
Now then, time to start extracting some magic.
She's nearby.
The mana feels stronger here.
Okay!
Whoever's behind this has a good deal of power.
We have to keep our guards up.
Please, Marie.
Hold on.
We're coming, kids.
Hang in there.
Now, everyone, please stay calm.
The Magic Knights will find your children and bring them home safely.
Whoa!
Get a look at a rope.
Are they really going to bring my son back to me?
Where are Marco and Luca?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, Pim.
It's all right.
Asta will bring them back.
I promise you.
Yes, they'll be home before you know it.
Okay.
But what happened to our house?
Yeah, that's another thing silly Asta will be taking care of.
For now, let's just patch it up the best we can, okay?
It's gonna be freezing in there.
Right.
I need to contact the other knights.
Hello there, Knights Headquarters here.
Hey, I recognize you.
They have you working at headquarters?
Ha ha!
Captain Jack stationed me here to help out temporarily, but I'm not gonna be a full-time paper pusher or anything.
I've just accomplished so much in my short time with the praying mantises that I've earned myself a little break from battle, you see?
Ha ha!
We've got an emergency here, you babbling idiot!
Listen, there's snow falling in neon!
Really?
How romantic.
Do you understand the word emergency?
Somebody used magic to make it snow so they can abduct children from the village!
Wait, huh?
You should tell the magic knights right away!
What do you think I'm doing now?
Right, well, don't worry.
Seke is on the case.
Ha ha!
I don't find that reassuring, idiot.
I'm picking up mana over there.
Yes, that's it!
The caves would be a perfect place to keep all of the children hidden.
Marco!
Hang on, Ghosh!
Can you set me down over there for a sec?
Leave him.
My angel's the only one who matters.
If you want off, then let go.
Ha ha!
Asta!
And you're a magic knight!
Don't they have standards anymore?
I couldn't care less what happens to anybody else.
As long as Marie stays safe.
Just like the captain told me the day I cast aside my prisoner's clothing and joined the Black Bulls.
I won't stop you.
Go on and protect whatever you think needs protecting.
And that's just what I'm gonna do.
Marco!
Stay with us.
The poor thing.
He's covered in scrapes and frostbitten, too.
Marco!
Can you hear me?
It's no use.
He's in some kind of trance.
All right.
Just leave it to me!
Wait!
What are you going to do?
Hold on.
What?
Asta...
Sister?
Hey, kid.
How are you feeling?
He dispelled the magic with the touch of his sword.
It hurts so much!
Hold on.
Flame healing magic.
Sacred healing light.
Thank you.
I'm a lot warmer now.
That's amazing, Granny.
You can use healing magic?
Tell us, child.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I don't really know.
Someone sure roughed him up.
Marco!
We've got to go rescue your sister and the rest of the kids.
Can you wait by yourself in that cave till we get back?
What?
Please, Asta.
It's scary in there.
Can't I stay with you?
Hey, what's with the tears?
You're a man now, aren't you?
Tell you what.
I'll lend you my Black Bulls robe, okay?
Just wear that and you'll forget all about being scared.
Can't tell by looking at it, but this baby's chock full of magic knight courage.
Now you sit tight until we come back, okay?
Okay, I will.
You get that it's just alone, though, don't you?
When we're done, you're gonna give it right back.
And don't even think about getting it all snotty.
Yeah, got it.
Come on.
We need to hurry.
I'm worried about the others.
It's amazing here, but the mana's getting stronger and stronger.
Marie, I'll be there soon.
Oh, yeah.
There we go.
I'm gonna squeeze every last drop of magic out of you whiny brats.
You'll be empty shells.
And done.
Now, let's see.
Is our little star ready?
No, please let me go.
Don't take my magic.
It's only going to get worse if you keep fighting.
Don't struggle, girl.
We've got plans for you.
That magic power of yours is gonna make us filthy rich.
Marie!
Big brother, I knew you'd come.
My angel, you're off.
You've hurt Marie, and for that you will die!
What do we do?
He's going to kill us.
And that robe, he's a magic knight.
Damn.
How did he find us so fast?
Are you waiting for an engraved invitation?
Attack him already!
Yes, sir.
Snow magic, snow cry!
Mirror magic, now, mirror shift!
You ever seen magic like that before?
I can't seem to hit him at all!
You'll be!
Hurry, try another spell, you moron!
Give me a second.
I'm going to try snow creation magic.
Now, friends!
That's it.
Help me, friends.
Go!
God damn it!
Taking out a few of these guys isn't going to do you any good.
These can make a million of his little friends if he needs to.
Please don't hurt him!
I'm done playing.
Mirror magic.
Reflect with brain!
I'll slaughter you all.
No way!
He killed them all.
Every last one.
How are we supposed to beat someone so powerful?
Damn it.
It wasn't supposed to play out like this.
I only took this job because it sounded easy.
Sucking the magic out of a bunch of kids.
I didn't plan on going up against a guy like this.
Nothing's working.
What now?
I need to think.
Shut up!
Come on.
There's got to be something we could do.
But what?
You better back off, Mirror Boy.
Or you won't like what I do to her next.
Don't you dare.
Do you really want to threaten me now?
If I get nervous, I might squeeze this a little too tight and bruise this delicate peach.
Go on, niece.
I don't think he's going to give us any more trouble.
Yes!
Damn!
Marie!
Everything's going to be all right, Angel.
I was there, you came!
Of course I did.
Are you okay?
You idiot!
What were you thinking launching an attack like that?
Any one of those projectiles could have hit Marie.
Take it easy!
I had to do it if I was going to save her.
And besides, you were a lot more likely to get hit with something.
Like you'd ever be able to hit me.
My love makes me invincible.
Stop, brother.
That's enough.
Move, Marie.
Nuh-uh.
These children have been completely drained of magic.
It's been taken.
And I don't know if they can ever regain it.
That's what they wanted?
That big scary man.
He said something about money.
What kind of monster are you?
Not good.
I don't like the way he's looking at us.
So what now?
That tall, angry one was bad enough on his own.
But now that his friends are here, we don't stand a chance.
This kid.
Hey, he's some kind of freak.
He doesn't have a scrap of magic power in him.
Can you believe it?
I didn't even know that was possible.
And look.
He's not wearing a robe.
That's no magic knight.
Just some stupid kid.
Let's split up these.
You take the girl's brother.
Meanwhile, I'll see what I can do about this little runt over here.
You won't get away with this.
I will make you pay!
This is for a long time.
Over here.
Hold on.
Oh
Holding down the fort
Luca, Marco
Don't you worry
I'm sure Asta and the others will have no problem
Bringing them back
Oh
I know what would take your mind off of it
A quiz
Okay
I'll go first
Where was Asta born?
In Hodge village
That's right
Okay, my turn now
How old is Asta?
He's 15 years old
Alright
When is Asta's birthday?
October 4th
Okay, what's his dream?
Let's see
It's to become the wizard king
That's right, isn't it?
You sure know a lot about him
And so do you
I'm not going to let her show me up
Ha ha, everyone
Feeling a bit down?
Nothing a little seki action won't cure
I'll be making quite the showing next time
Hoo-ha, hoo-ho-ha
Page 32
Three leaf sprouts
Get ready for maximum
Ha ha
Mom
I don't know
Hello
No
You must have been
I don't know
Aten
My belt
About me
I don't know
You may be